So, now let's talk about guardrails in Amazon Bedrock.
So, guardrails allow you to control the interaction between your users and your foundation
models.
So, you can set up guardrails to filter, undesirable, and harmful content.
For example, say we have Amazon Bedrock and we set up a guardrail to block any kind
of food recipes.
And the user is using your model and saying, "Hey, suggest me something to cook tonight."
Then, Amazon Bedrock will respond, "Sorry, this is a restricted topic.
This is because we have set up a guardrail to block this topic."
Of course, maybe you don't want to block food recipes, but something a bit more relevant
to your business.
You can also use guardrails to remove any personally identifiable information or PII to make
sure that your users are safe.
You can also enhance privacy and you can reduce hallucinations.
We'll see what hallucinations are later on this course, but the idea is that you want to
make sure that the answers are safe and sound and that they are not just invented of
the block.
So, guardrails can help you with that.
You can also create multiple guardrails and multiple level guardrails.
And you can also monitor and analyze all the user inputs that will violate the guardrails
to make sure that you have set the guardrails up properly.
So, that's it.
Just a short intro to the guardrail.
I hope you liked it and I will see you in the next lecture.